A Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files, 1976-1991
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files 1976-1991
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1.951
This collection consists of 5,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions apply only to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1995 March 8.
Scope and Content Information
Topical files from Dean Robert T. Canevari's office, including files on individual fraternities and sororities.
Organization
Series I: General Records Boxes 1-18
Series II: Sororities Boxes 19-21
Series III: Fraternities Boxes 22-25
Series IV: Restricted materials Boxes 26
Contents List
- Series I: General Records
  - Activities Coordinating Committee 1987-1990 (Box 1)
  - Administration, Vice President For Administration 1986-1989 (Box 1)
  - Admissions, Office of 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action--Miscellaneous 1988 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs, Office of (see also University Union) 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - OAAA Task Force--Rec #16 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - ACE White Paper on Alcohol Abuse 1985 (Box 1)
  - Alcohol Awareness 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - Alcohol Policy 1988 (Box 1)
  - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award--Miscellaneous 1986-1988 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association--Correspondence and Miscellaneous 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - Apartheid Simulation Proposal 1990 (Box 1)
  - Architecture 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Sciences Career Forum 1989 (Box 1)
  - Asian Student Leaders Conference 1989 (Box 1)
  - Athletic Department 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - Auxiliary Services, Assistant Vice President For 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Bad Check Committee 1985-1989 (Box 1)
  - Bed Building Committee (1 of 3) 1989-1991 (Box 1)
  - Bed Building Committee (2-3 of 3) 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Black Fraternities/Sororities, Video Teleconference 1990 (Box 2)
  - Black Virginia Alumni 1985-1989 (Box 2)
  - Blagden (Gus) Committee (3 folders) 1987-1990 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors--Ad Hoc Committee on Inter-group Relations 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors--Finance Committee 1990 (Box 2)
  - Budget--Dean of Students Office---2 folders 1986-1988 (Box 2)
  - Budget (2 folders) 1987-1989 (Box 2)
  - Budget--Dean of Students Office--Residence Staff 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Budget--Newcomb Hall 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Budget--Student Activities Business Manager 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Budget--Addendum Process 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Budget--Collaboration Virginia 1990 (Box 2)
  - Budget--DATS Monthly and Budget Variance Report 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Budgett--Dean of Students and RLO Budget Addendum Process 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Salary Recommendations (Restricted) 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Ten Year Capital Budget Program (2 folders) 1986 (Box 3)
  - Bursar's Office 1985-1989 (Box 3)
  - Business and Finance, Vice President For. 1982-1989 (Box 3)
  - Business and Finance--Sandridge, Student Committee--Services in Businesses and Finance Areas 1989 (Box 3)
  - Cavalier Daily 1988-1990 (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville and Albermarle County--Miscellaneous 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Colonnades 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Common Reading Experience 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Computer Capabilities 1982-1988 (Box 3)
  - Contracted Independent Organization, CIO (2 folders) 1987-1989 (Box 3)
  - Council of the Stone Table 1984-1989 (Box 3)
  - Dining Services Committee (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - DOS Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - DOS Retreat 1990 (Box 4)
  - DOS Staff Meetings 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Development Office 1987 (Box 4)
  - Dining Services 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Drugs--Miscellaneous 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Easters 1979-1988 (Box 4)
  - Entering Students 1986-1989 (Box 4)
  - Equal Opportunity Employer 1986-1990 (Box 4)
  - Ernest H. Ern---VPSA (2 folders) 1987-1990 (Box 4)
  - Exit Interviews--Robert T. Canevari Office (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Expansion 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Program 1987-1989 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Handbook 1987-1989 (Box 5)
  - Film Policy 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Finance, Assistant Vice President of 1985-1987 (Box 5)
  - Financial Aid 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Finals Planning 1990 (Box 5)
  - Fine Arts 1986-1989 (Box 5)
  - First Year Council 1986-1990 (Box 5)
  - First Year Seminar--Approach to thinking about 1987-1989 (Box 5)
  - First Year Seminar Expenses 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - First Year Student Profile--ACE Survey Report 1988 (Box 5)
  - First Year Student Profile--ACE Greek Organizations on College Campuses 1989 (Box 5)
  - Fraternities, Alumni Advisory Committee 1989 (Box 5)
  - Fraternity Alumni Association 1984-1988 (Box 6)
  - Fraternities--CIO and Constitution 1987-1990 (Box 6)
  - Fraternities--CIO Correspondence 1987 (Box 6)
  - Fraternities--Fire Safety Inspection Program 1987-1989 (Box 6)
  - Fraternities--Inter Fraternity Council (2 folders) 1986-1989 (Box 6)
  - Fraternity--Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1986-1990 (Box 6)
  - Fraternities/Sororities--Board of Visitors Hearing 1942 October 3 (Box 6)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, Commission on 1979-1980 (Box 6)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Scholarship Rankings 1988, Spring (Box 6)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, White Paper on 1988 (Box 6)
  - Glee Club University 1988-1989 (Box 6)
  - Graduating Class and Trustees 1988-1990 (Box 6)
  - Graduate Roundtables 1988-1990 (Box 6)
  - Gary Carrington Candidates (Restricted) 1990, Feb. (Box 7)
  - Gary Carrington Nominating Committee (Restricted) 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Gary Carrington Nominees (Restricted) 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Hazing 1987-1989 (Box 7)
  - Handicapped Concerns 1984-1990 (Box 7)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation (2 folders) 1988-1990 (Box 7)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation, Alumni Council of 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Honor Committee (2 folders) 1988-1990 (Box 7)
  - Home Run of Virginia 1989 (Box 7)
  - Housing Division 1988-1990 (Box 7)
  - Housing Possibilities, New 1989 (Box 7)
  - IFC--National Greek Collaboration 1989 (Box 8)
  - Institute for Substance Abuse Studies 1988 Oct. (Box 8)
  - Institute for Substance Abuse Studies--Alcohol and Marijuana Abuse among First Year College Students Planning to Join Frats and Sororities n.d. (Box 8)
  - Institute for Substance Abuse Studies--Psychosocial Inventory Amonth First Year College Students by Patterns of Alcohol Use! n.d. (Box 8)
  - Institute for Substance Abuse Studies--Risk Taking Behavior of College Students n.d. (Box 8)
  - Institute for Substance Abuse Studies--Are Fraternities and Sororities Risk Factors For Alcohol Abuse Among First Year College Students" n.d. (Box 8)
  - Judiciary 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Judiciary Committee 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Judiciary Committee--Arbitration Board 1976-1986 (Box 8)
  - Judiciary Committee--Canevari vs. Cataldo and Urana 1990 Fall (Box 8)
  - UCJP--Culp v. McCall (Restricted) 1990 (Box 8)
  - Lawn, The 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Leadership--Summer Leader Program 1990 (Box 8)
  - Leadership Workshops 1987-1989 (Box 8)
  - Madison House Fundraising, Sub-Committee on 1990 (Box 8)
  - Madison House Board of Directors 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Media Board of Directors 1976-1987 (Box 8)
  - Monroe Hill Residential College 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - Monroe Hill Residential College Committee 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - Multiculturalism Expenses 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - Newcomb Hall Director's Office 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - Newcomb/Peabody/Lambeth/Student Activities Building 1984-1986 (Box 9)
  - Newcomb Director's Office 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Articles--MiscellaneousUVa Misc. Newspaper Articles 1988-1990 (Box 9)
  - Annual Report and Degree Registrant Database 1988 Jul-1990 Dec (Box 9)
  - On Target Expenses 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - On Target Program 1988-1990 (Box 9)
  - Orientation 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - Parents Funding (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - Parents Fund 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Parents Weekend (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - Parking and Transit Study-- Building Committee (1 of 2) 1988-1990 (Box 10)
  - Parking and Transit Study-- Building Committee (2 of 2) 1988-1990 (Box 11)
  - Transportation and Parking, Committee on 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Parking and Transportation 1986-1989 (Box 11)
  - Parking and Transportation Committee 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Pavilion VIII 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Pavilion VIII Meeting 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Pavilion XI 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Pep Band 1988-1990 (Box 11)
  - Performance Evaluations 1988 (Box 11)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Incident 1988, Oct. (Box 11)
  - Physical Plant 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Planning--Biennial Evaluation and Planning Report, Dean of Students (4 folders) 1982-1990 (Box 12)
  - Planning--Guidelines For Planning 1984-1990 (Box 12)
  - President's Office 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - Program Coordination Group 1990 (Box 12)
  - Recommendations (other than students) 1980-1986 (Box 12)
  - Research, Association Vice President on 1986-1989 (Box 12)
  - Residence Life Office 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - Residence Staff (2 folders) 1988-1990 (Box 13)
  - Resident Staff Serious Incident Reports 1989-1991 (Box 13)
  - Resident Staff--Corl Subcommittee On Expansion Minutes 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Resident Staff, Committee on (3 folders) 1987-1990 (Box 13)
  - Resident Staff--Corl Subcommittee on Expansion, Final Report 1989 April (Box 14)
  - Resident Staff--Rugby Road Study Group 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Resident Staff--Committee to Clarify Solicitation Regulations 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - Resident Staff--Senior Resident Interviews 1990 Spring (Box 14)
  - Resident Staff--Summer Resident Staff 1989 (Box 14)
  - Resident Staff--Senior Residents Promotion 1989 (Box 14)
  - Resident Staff--24 Hour Lock Up Case 1987 (Box 14)
  - Security Work Group 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Sexual Assault--Miscellaneous 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - Sexual Assault Policy 1985-1990 (Box 15)
  - Smoking Policy 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Sororities 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - Sororities--Inter-Sorority Council 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Sororities--Inter-Sorority Council-CIO Constitution 1987-1990 (Box 15)
  - Strategic Planning-Peabody/Newcomb 1984-1988 (Box 15)
  - Stress, Task Force On 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - Student Affairs Employee Council 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Student Affairs Staff Development 1986-1990 (Box 15)
  - Student Council 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Student Council 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - Student Council Fall Registration 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - Student Health 1988-1990 (Box 16)
  - Student Health Suspensions (3 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - Student Organizations--Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1988-1990 (Box 16)
  - Substance Abuse Consortium (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - Summer Student Leader Roundtables 1989 (Box 17)
  - Summer Session 1986-1990 (Box 17)
  - Summer Session Committee 1988 (Box 17)
  - Summer Session-- Annual Report 1989 (Box 17)
  - Transfer Students 1986-1989 (Box 17)
  - University Police 1988-1989 (Box 17)
  - University Union 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - University Union (relationship with OAAA) 1985 (Box 17)
  - University Union--Rent Discussions--University Hall 1974-1986 (Box 17)
  - University Union 1988-1989 (Box 17)
  - Virginia Consortium 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Virginia Forum On Campus Crime Prevention 1989 June 6 (Box 17)
  - Volunteerism Conference--Planning Committee 1988 (Box 18)
  - Wellness Committee 1988-1989 (Box 18)
  - Wellness Committee 1988-1987 (Box 18)
  - Women, Task Force on Status of 1987 (Box 18)
  - Women's Studies 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - WTJU 1986-1990 (Box 18)
- Series II: Sororities
  - Alpha Chi Omega 1986-1989 (Box 19)
  - Alpha Delta Pi 1986-1990 (Box 19)
  - Alpha Gamma Delta 1988-1990 (Box 19)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha 1988-1990 (Box 19)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi 1986-1989 (Box 19)
  - Alpha Pi 1986-1989 (Box 19)
  - Alpha Sigma Alpha 1988-1990 (Box 19)
  - Alpha Xi Delta 1986-1990 (Box 19)
  - Alpha Xi Delta 1986-1990 (Box 19)
  - Chi Omega 1987-1990 (Box 20)
  - Delta Delta Delta 1986-1991 (Box 20)
  - Delta Gamma 1986-1991 (Box 20)
  - Delta Sigma Theta 1987-1989 (Box 20)
  - Delta Zeta 1986-1990 (Box 20)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta 1987-1990 (Box 20)
  - Kappa Delta 1987-1990 (Box 20)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma 1987-1990 (Box 20)
  - Phi Mu 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - Phi Beta Phi 1986-1990 (Box 21)
  - Sigma Delta Tau 1986-1988 (Box 21)
  - Sigma Gamma RHO 1987-1990 (Box 21)
  - Sigma Kappa 1986-1990 (Box 21)
  - Sigma Sigma Sigma 1987-1990 (Box 21)
  - Zeta Phi Beta 1987-1990 (Box 21)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha 1987-1990 (Box 21)
- Series III: Fraternities
  - Alpha Delta Phi 1987-1991 (Box 22)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi 1987-1990 (Box 22)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha 1986-1990 (Box 22)
  - Alumni Programs 1981-1982 (Box 22)
  - Beta Theta Pi 1987-1990 (Box 22)
  - Chi Phi 1987-1990 (Box 22)
  - Chi Psi 1987-1990 (Box 22)
  - Committee on Fraternities/Sororities Minutes 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon 1987-1991 (Box 22)
  - Delta Sigma Phi n.d. (Box 22)
  - Delta Tau Delta 1987-1990 (Box 22)
  - Delta Upsilon 1987-1990 (Box 23)
  - Gamma Gamma, Order of Omega 1989 (Box 23)
  - Gamma Nu Si 1982-1984 (Box 23)
  - Kappa Alpha 1987-1990 (Box 23)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi 1987-1989 (Box 23)
  - Kappa Sigma 1987-1990 (Box 23)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma 1987-1990 (Box 23)
  - Phi Kappa Psi 1987-1990 (Box 23)
  - Phi Beta Sigma 1987-1990 (Box 23)
  - Phi Epsilon 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - Phi Gamma Delta 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - Omega Psi Phi 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - Pi Kappa Phi 1983-1990 (Box 24)
  - Pi Lambda Phi 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - St. Anthony Hall (Delta Psi) 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - St. Elmo Hall (Delta phi) 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon 1983-1990 (Box 24)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - Sigma Chi 1987-1990 (Box 25)
  - Sigma Phi 1987-1990 (Box 25)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1986-1990 (Box 25)
  - Sigma Nu 1987-1990 (Box 25)
  - Sigma Pi 1987-1990 (Box 25)
  - Tau Epsilon Phi 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - Theta Chi 1987-1990 (Box 25)
  - Theta Delta Chi 1987-1990 (Box 25)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon 1987-1990 (Box 25)
  - Zeta Psi 1987-1990 (Box 25)
- Series IV: Restricted material (Box 26)